https://dalzielpark.co.uk/privacy-policy

ABOUT THIS POLICY
Lisini Pub Company is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible way. This policy outlines how we aim to achieve this and includes the information collected when:– you use our website– you make a booking on our website– you make enquiries on our website– someone is interested in working with us
DEFINITION OF PERSONAL DATA
Personal Data means any data that relates to an identifiable person who can be directly/indirectly identified from that data. In this case, it means personal data that you give to us via our site.By providing your personal data, you agree that we can use your personal data in accordance with this policy.Ensure you understand this policy in its entirety and take your time to read it.
WHO ARE WE?
Lisini Pub Company is a family owned pub company based in Uddingston. We are a group of venues based across the Lanarkshire area. Our registered address is: 33 Laird Street, Coatbridge, ML5 3LW
HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?
We collect information from you:– when you make a booking – when you visit a restaurant (preferences, allergies etc.) – make an enquiry– when you sign up to marketing emails
WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED FROM YOU?
You may be asked to submit personal information about yourself when you make a booking. We will collect this information so we can fulfill your booking request and you may dine at our venue.When you make a booking:– title– name– e-mail address – use in the case of no-shows (where applicable)– telephone number– company name– dietary requests– marketing preferences (whether you opt-in or opt-out)– Home OR work address– Feedback emails– Payment details stored and encrypted with 3rd party applicationsWhen you dine with Lisini Pub Company:– marketing responses (where applicable)– survey responses– current and past restaurant reservation detailsWhen you access our sites:There is “Device Information” about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Lisini Pub Company. This information can include:– device type (e.g. mobile, computer, laptop, tablet)– cookies– operating system– IP address– browser type– browser information (e.g., type, language, and history)– domain names– access times– settings– referring website addresses– other data about your device to provide the services as otherwise described in this policy.Location information:If you use our website, we may receive your generic location (such as city or neighbourhood).Careers:You may submit your CV if you’re interested in working for us to jobs@lisini.co.uk . This information may include:– personal details– employment details– education– salary history– other relevant detailsWe will use this information to assess your application. We may also keep it in our records for future reference. Please get in contact if you would no longer like us to hold your records.
HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED?
Our use of your personal data will always have a lawful basis, either because it is necessary to complete a booking, because you have consented to our use of your personal data (e.g. by subscribing to emails), or because it is in our legitimate interests.We require the information outlined in the previous section to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:– Internal record keeping.– To send you service emails (booking confirmation and post-dining feedback).– To improve our products and services.– To send marketing communications if you have opted in to receive them.– We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION?
We will not sell, distribute, or lease your personal information to third parties. Any personal information we request from you will be safeguarded under current legislation.We will only share your information with companies if necessary to deliver services on our behalf. For example service providers (e.g. ResDiary for the provision of online bookings), third-party payment processors, and other third parties to provide our Sites and fulfil your requests, and as otherwise consented to by you or as permitted by applicable law.Third parties whose content appears on our Site may use third-party Cookies, as detailed below. Please refer to ‘Use of Cookies’ for more information on controlling Cookies. Please note that we do not control the activities of such third parties, nor the data they collect and use and advise you to check the privacy policies of any such third parties.You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information at any point. Please refer to the Your Choices section of this Privacy Policy for details.
HOW AND WHERE DO WE STORE YOUR DATA?
We only keep your personal data for as long as we need to, in order to use it as described in this privacy policy, and/or for as long as we have your permission to keep it.– For reservations taken through ResDiary software, your data will only be stored in the UK. ResDiary data is stored securely in data centres managed by Rackspace.– For enquiries taken through the website, your data will be stored in the UK, and managed by Microsoft Office 365.– For bookings made direct with Lisini Pub Co for one of our hotels, your data will be stored with HOP hosted platform and hosted within the UK.– All other 3rd party products used by Lisini Pub Company will store your data within the UK and featured guidelines can be provided.We may analyse your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of additional information about you when it is available from external sources to help us do this effectively.
YOUR CHOICES
We will not contact you for marketing purposes by email, phone or text message unless you have given your prior consent. We will not pass your details to any third parties for marketing purposes unless you have expressly permitted us to. Furthermore, you can change your marketing preferences at any time by contacting usYou have a right to request a copy of the personal information that Lisini Pub Company holds about you and have any inaccuracies corrected.You have the right to withdraw your consent to us using your personal data at any time, and to request that we delete it. We do not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. Data retention will be determined on the following basis:Retention is not based on a time of data held, but rather the consent that you give us, this will be subject to change as legislation changes.
SECURITY
Data security is very important to us, and to protect your data we have taken suitable measures to safeguard and secure data collected through our Site.
USE OF COOKIES
Like many other websites, we use cookies. We use them to help you personalise your online experience.A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server which allows the website to recognise you when you visit. Cookies only collect data about browsing actions and patterns, and do not identify you as an individual.We use cookies for the following purposes:– Authentication, personalisation and security: cookies help us verify your account and device and determine when you log in, so we can make it easier for you to access the services and provide the appropriate experiences and features. We also use cookies to help prevent fraudulent use of login credentials.– Performance and analytics: cookies help us analyse how the services are being accessed and used, and enable us to track the performance of the services. For example, we use cookies to determine if you viewed a page or opened an email. This helps us provide you with information that you find interesting. We also use cookies to provide insights regarding your End Users and your sites’ performance, such as page views, conversion rates, device information, visitor IP addresses, and referral sites.– Third Parties: Third Party services may use cookies to help you sign into their services from our services. We also may use third-party cookies, such as Google Analytics, to assist with analysing performance. Any third party cookie usage is governed by the privacy policy of the third party placing the cookie.– Opting Out: You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use the services.Our Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
OUR GROUP
We may share your information (such as meal or seating preferences and special occasions) with other venues within the Lisini Pub Company Group. This is to enhance the hospitality experience that we (the group) provide you when you dine with us (such as, trying to seat you by a window, if you previously expressed a preference for window seating) (“customised service”) and to improve our table and shift planning.In addition to providing you with more customised service, we may, as permitted by applicable law, share your information with our restaurant affiliates to support operations, such as to perform analytics, tailor marketing to you, support a loyalty program that you have chosen to participate in, and improve services.For more information, please feel free to contact us.
CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Lisini Pub Company will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Lisini Pub Company encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Lisini Pub Company is protecting your information. This policy was last updated in April 2020.In addition to providing you with more customised service, we may, as permitted by applicable law, share your information with our restaurant affiliates to support operations, such as to perform analytics, tailor marketing to you, support a loyalty program that you have chosen to participate in, and improve services.For more information, please feel free to contact us.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Lisini Pub Company welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Lisini Pub Company has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact Lisini Pub Company. We will aim to use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
We're Social
Follow us on our various social media platforms to keep up with all the latest offers and events going on here at The Dalziel Park Hotel & Golf Club in Motherwell, North Lanarkshire.
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Linkedin
Tripadvisor
FIND US
Dalziel Park Hotel & Golf Club
100 Hagen Drive, Motherwell, ML1 5RZ
LISINI PUB COMPANY, 114 MAIN STREET, UDDINGSTON, G71 7HZ01698 812106 | DALZIEL@LISINI.CO.UKCompany Number: SC262192  |  VAT: 829963767
